# William Hathaway

Front-end Web Developer with a background in design and visual art. Focused and driven when it comes to implementing a vision and solving problems, with experience in JavaScript, NodeJS, CSS, and SQL

2 Old Goshen Rd Williamsburg, MA (413) 326 4769 william.hathaway38@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# InResonance, Northampton, MA — Technical Writer

SEPT 2017 - FEBRUARY 2018

Writing documentation for web design using the Schoolyard Builder tool.

### InResonance, Northampton, MA — Development Intern

MAY 2016 - AUGUST 2016

Working in the development department creating in-house database manipulation for processing clients' information using SQL.

## **EDUCATION**

### Trilogy Education Coding Boot Camp, Harvard Extension School

SEPT 2018 - MARCH 2019

Currently enrolled in the Full Stack Coding Bootcamp with the Trilogy Education Department at Harvard Extension School.

# Greenfield Community College, Greenfield, MA

JAN 2019 - MAY 2019

Studied design and animation using Processing.

## Hampshire College, Amherst, MA — Division 1

SEPT 2016 - MAY 2017

Studied design, philosophy and physics.

#### **PROJECTS**

# Cloud Compare — Coding Bootcamp Project 1

A web application for comparing the content of different news sites, using API calls and Highcharts

#### **LINKS**

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/william-hathaway-731b7a190/

Portfolio:

https://willhathaway.github.io/Portfolio/

GitHub:

https://github.com/willhathaway

#### **SKILLS**

Full Stack Web Development

Graphic Design

Interface Design

Visual Art

## **AWARDS**

Bootcamp Project 1:

- Most Disruptive
- Best Use of Tech
- Most Socially Conscious

#### **LANGUAGES**

JavaScript NodeJS React